{
    "irrelevant": [
        {
            "model_response": "No, he is not.",
            "needle": "Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "How long has Elon Musk been X Corp.'s CEO?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "No, he is not.",
            "needle": "Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "How long has Elon Musk been X Corp.'s CEO?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "No, he is not.",
            "needle": "Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "How long has Elon Musk been X Corp.'s CEO?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "No, he is not.",
            "needle": "Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "How long has Elon Musk been X Corp.'s CEO?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "No, he is not.",
            "needle": "Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "How long has Elon Musk been X Corp.'s CEO?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "No, Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "needle": "Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "How long has Elon Musk been X Corp.'s CEO?",
            "frequency": 11,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "No, Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "needle": "Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "How long has Elon Musk been X Corp.'s CEO?",
            "frequency": 11,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "No, Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "needle": "Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "How long has Elon Musk been X Corp.'s CEO?",
            "frequency": 11,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "No, Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "needle": "Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "How long has Elon Musk been X Corp.'s CEO?",
            "frequency": 11,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "No, Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "needle": "Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "How long has Elon Musk been X Corp.'s CEO?",
            "frequency": 11,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "No, Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "needle": "Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "How long has Elon Musk been X Corp.'s CEO?",
            "frequency": 11,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "No, Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "needle": "Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "How long has Elon Musk been X Corp.'s CEO?",
            "frequency": 11,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "No, Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO. In 2023 and 2024, OpenAI faced multiple lawsuits for alleged copyright infringement against authors and media",
            "needle": "Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "How long has Elon Musk been X Corp.'s CEO?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "No, Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "needle": "Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "How long has Elon Musk been X Corp.'s CEO?",
            "frequency": 11,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "No, Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO. According to OpenAI, the capped-profit model allows OpenAI Global, LLC to legally attract investment from venture funds and, in addition",
            "needle": "Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "How long has Elon Musk been X Corp.'s CEO?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "No, Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "needle": "Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "How long has Elon Musk been X Corp.'s CEO?",
            "frequency": 11,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "No, Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "needle": "Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "How long has Elon Musk been X Corp.'s CEO?",
            "frequency": 11,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "No, Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO. OpenAI, Inc. is an American artificial intelligence (AI) research organization founded in December 2015 and headquartered in San Francisco, California",
            "needle": "Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "How long has Elon Musk been X Corp.'s CEO?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "No, Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO. In 2019, OpenAI transitioned from a non-profit to a for-profit company, with the profit being capped at",
            "needle": "Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "How long has Elon Musk been X Corp.'s CEO?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "No, Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO. Google announced a similar AI application (Bard), after ChatGPT was launched, fearing that ChatGPT could threaten Google's place as",
            "needle": "Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "How long has Elon Musk been X Corp.'s CEO?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "No, Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO. In 2018, Musk resigned from his Board of Directors seat, citing a potential conflict of interest with his role as CEO of",
            "needle": "Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "How long has Elon Musk been X Corp.'s CEO?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "No, Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "needle": "Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "How long has Elon Musk been X Corp.'s CEO?",
            "frequency": 11,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "No, Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO. OpenAI's potential and mission drew these researchers to the firm; a Google employee said he was willing to leave Google for OpenAI \"partly because of",
            "needle": "Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "How long has Elon Musk been X Corp.'s CEO?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "No, Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO. According to OpenAI, the preview received over a million signups within the first five days. According to anonymous sources cited by Reuters in December 2",
            "needle": "Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "How long has Elon Musk been X Corp.'s CEO?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "No, Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO. In May 2024, significant leadership changes occurred as Chief Scientist Ilya Sutskever resigned\u2014being succeeded by Jakub P",
            "needle": "Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "How long has Elon Musk been X Corp.'s CEO?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        }
    ],
    "irrelevant_misleading": [
        {
            "model_response": "No, he is not.",
            "needle": "Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "How long has Elon Musk been X Corp.'s CEO?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "No, he is not.",
            "needle": "Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "How long has Elon Musk been X Corp.'s CEO?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "No, he is not.",
            "needle": "Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "How long has Elon Musk been X Corp.'s CEO?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "No, he is not.",
            "needle": "Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "How long has Elon Musk been X Corp.'s CEO?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "No, he is not.",
            "needle": "Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "How long has Elon Musk been X Corp.'s CEO?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Yes, Elon Musk is still X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "needle": "Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "How long has Elon Musk been X Corp.'s CEO?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "No, Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "needle": "Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "How long has Elon Musk been X Corp.'s CEO?",
            "frequency": 8,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "No, Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "needle": "Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "How long has Elon Musk been X Corp.'s CEO?",
            "frequency": 8,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "No, Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "needle": "Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "How long has Elon Musk been X Corp.'s CEO?",
            "frequency": 8,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "No, Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "needle": "Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "How long has Elon Musk been X Corp.'s CEO?",
            "frequency": 8,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Yes, Elon Musk is still X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "needle": "Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "How long has Elon Musk been X Corp.'s CEO?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "No, Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "needle": "Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "How long has Elon Musk been X Corp.'s CEO?",
            "frequency": 8,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "No, Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO. In 2023 and 2024, OpenAI faced multiple lawsuits for alleged copyright infringement against authors and media",
            "needle": "Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "How long has Elon Musk been X Corp.'s CEO?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "No, Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO. Microsoft's Peter Lee stated that the cost of a top AI researcher exceeds the cost of a top NFL quarterback prospect. OpenAI's potential",
            "needle": "Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "How long has Elon Musk been X Corp.'s CEO?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "No, Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO. OpenAI, a non-profit artificial intelligence research organization, was founded in 2015 by Elon Musk and other prominent technology entrepreneurs",
            "needle": "Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "How long has Elon Musk been X Corp.'s CEO?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "No, Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO. He resigned from the position in 2023 and was replaced by Sam Altman.",
            "needle": "Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "How long has Elon Musk been X Corp.'s CEO?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "No, Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "needle": "Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "How long has Elon Musk been X Corp.'s CEO?",
            "frequency": 8,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "No, Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO. According to an investigation led by TechCrunch, while YC Research never contributed any funds, Open Philanthropy contributed $30 million and another $1",
            "needle": "Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "How long has Elon Musk been X Corp.'s CEO?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "No, Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "needle": "Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "How long has Elon Musk been X Corp.'s CEO?",
            "frequency": 8,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "No, Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO. Rumors of this deal suggested that Microsoft may receive 75% of OpenAI's profits until it secures its investment return and a 4",
            "needle": "Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "How long has Elon Musk been X Corp.'s CEO?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Yes, Elon Musk is still X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "needle": "Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "How long has Elon Musk been X Corp.'s CEO?",
            "frequency": 3,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "No, Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "needle": "Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "How long has Elon Musk been X Corp.'s CEO?",
            "frequency": 8,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "No, Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO. OpenAI's potential and mission drew these researchers to the firm; a Google employee said he was willing to leave Google for OpenAI \"partly because of",
            "needle": "Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "How long has Elon Musk been X Corp.'s CEO?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "No, Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO. In December 2022, OpenAI received widespread media coverage after launching a free preview of ChatGPT, its new AI",
            "needle": "Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "How long has Elon Musk been X Corp.'s CEO?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "No, Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO. In February, amidst SEC probes and investigations into CEO Altman's communications OpenAI unveiled its text-to-video model",
            "needle": "Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "How long has Elon Musk been X Corp.'s CEO?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        }
    ],
    "relevant": [
        {
            "model_response": "No, he is not.",
            "needle": "Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "How long has Elon Musk been X Corp.'s CEO?",
            "frequency": 12,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "No, he is not.",
            "needle": "Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "How long has Elon Musk been X Corp.'s CEO?",
            "frequency": 12,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "No, he is not.",
            "needle": "Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "How long has Elon Musk been X Corp.'s CEO?",
            "frequency": 12,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "No, he is not.",
            "needle": "Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "How long has Elon Musk been X Corp.'s CEO?",
            "frequency": 12,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "No, he is not.",
            "needle": "Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "How long has Elon Musk been X Corp.'s CEO?",
            "frequency": 12,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Yes, Elon Musk is still X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "needle": "Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "How long has Elon Musk been X Corp.'s CEO?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "No, Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "needle": "Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "How long has Elon Musk been X Corp.'s CEO?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "No, he is not.",
            "needle": "Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "How long has Elon Musk been X Corp.'s CEO?",
            "frequency": 12,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "No, Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO. Elon Musk is the CEO of Tesla, Inc. and SpaceX, and he is also the CEO of X Corp.",
            "needle": "Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "How long has Elon Musk been X Corp.'s CEO?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "No, Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO. In June, Musk told Twitter employees that Twitter is a \"digital town square\" that should be all-encompassing, like WeChat.",
            "needle": "Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "How long has Elon Musk been X Corp.'s CEO?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Yes, he is.",
            "needle": "Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "How long has Elon Musk been X Corp.'s CEO?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "No, Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "needle": "Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "How long has Elon Musk been X Corp.'s CEO?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Yes, Elon Musk is still X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "needle": "Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "How long has Elon Musk been X Corp.'s CEO?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "No, he is not.",
            "needle": "Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "How long has Elon Musk been X Corp.'s CEO?",
            "frequency": 12,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "No, he is not.",
            "needle": "Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "How long has Elon Musk been X Corp.'s CEO?",
            "frequency": 12,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Yes, Elon Musk is still X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "needle": "Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "How long has Elon Musk been X Corp.'s CEO?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "No, Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "needle": "Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "How long has Elon Musk been X Corp.'s CEO?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "No, he is not.",
            "needle": "Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "How long has Elon Musk been X Corp.'s CEO?",
            "frequency": 12,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "No, he is not.",
            "needle": "Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "How long has Elon Musk been X Corp.'s CEO?",
            "frequency": 12,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "No, he is not.",
            "needle": "Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "How long has Elon Musk been X Corp.'s CEO?",
            "frequency": 12,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Yes, Elon Musk is still X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "needle": "Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "How long has Elon Musk been X Corp.'s CEO?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "No, Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "needle": "Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "How long has Elon Musk been X Corp.'s CEO?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "No, Linda Yaccarino is the CEO of X Corp.",
            "needle": "Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "How long has Elon Musk been X Corp.'s CEO?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "No, he is not.",
            "needle": "Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "How long has Elon Musk been X Corp.'s CEO?",
            "frequency": 12,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "No, Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "needle": "Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "How long has Elon Musk been X Corp.'s CEO?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        }
    ],
    "relevant_misleading": [
        {
            "model_response": "No, he is not.",
            "needle": "Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "How long has Elon Musk been X Corp.'s CEO?",
            "frequency": 11,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "No, he is not.",
            "needle": "Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "How long has Elon Musk been X Corp.'s CEO?",
            "frequency": 11,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "No, he is not.",
            "needle": "Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "How long has Elon Musk been X Corp.'s CEO?",
            "frequency": 11,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "No, he is not.",
            "needle": "Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "How long has Elon Musk been X Corp.'s CEO?",
            "frequency": 11,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "No, he is not.",
            "needle": "Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "context_length": 0,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "How long has Elon Musk been X Corp.'s CEO?",
            "frequency": 11,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Yes, Elon Musk is still X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "needle": "Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "How long has Elon Musk been X Corp.'s CEO?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "No, Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "needle": "Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "How long has Elon Musk been X Corp.'s CEO?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "No, Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO. Elon Musk is the CEO of Tesla, Inc. and SpaceX, and he is also the CEO of X Corp.",
            "needle": "Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "How long has Elon Musk been X Corp.'s CEO?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "No, Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "needle": "Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "How long has Elon Musk been X Corp.'s CEO?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "No, Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO. In June, Musk told Twitter employees that Twitter is a \"digital town square\" that should be all-encompassing, like WeChat.",
            "needle": "Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "context_length": 1250,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "How long has Elon Musk been X Corp.'s CEO?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Yes, Elon Musk is still X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "needle": "Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "How long has Elon Musk been X Corp.'s CEO?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "No, Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "needle": "Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "How long has Elon Musk been X Corp.'s CEO?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "No, he is not.",
            "needle": "Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "How long has Elon Musk been X Corp.'s CEO?",
            "frequency": 11,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "No, he is not.",
            "needle": "Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "How long has Elon Musk been X Corp.'s CEO?",
            "frequency": 11,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "No, he is not.",
            "needle": "Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "context_length": 2500,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "How long has Elon Musk been X Corp.'s CEO?",
            "frequency": 11,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Yes, Elon Musk is still X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "needle": "Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "How long has Elon Musk been X Corp.'s CEO?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "No, Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "needle": "Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "How long has Elon Musk been X Corp.'s CEO?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "No, he is not.",
            "needle": "Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "How long has Elon Musk been X Corp.'s CEO?",
            "frequency": 11,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "No, he is not.",
            "needle": "Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "How long has Elon Musk been X Corp.'s CEO?",
            "frequency": 11,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "No, he is not.",
            "needle": "Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "context_length": 3750,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "How long has Elon Musk been X Corp.'s CEO?",
            "frequency": 11,
            "hallucination_type": "Correct Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "Yes, Elon Musk is still X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "needle": "Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 0.0,
            "question": "How long has Elon Musk been X Corp.'s CEO?",
            "frequency": 4,
            "hallucination_type": "Contradictory Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "No, Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "needle": "Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 100.0,
            "question": "How long has Elon Musk been X Corp.'s CEO?",
            "frequency": 5,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "No, Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO. He has been replaced by Linda Yaccarino, who is now the company's CEO.",
            "needle": "Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 25.0,
            "question": "How long has Elon Musk been X Corp.'s CEO?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "No, Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO. This led to a lawsuit by X Corp. against Media Matters, alleging that they had \"exploited\" the platform into making the ads",
            "needle": "Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 50.0,
            "question": "How long has Elon Musk been X Corp.'s CEO?",
            "frequency": 1,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        },
        {
            "model_response": "No, Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO. In June, Musk told Twitter employees that Twitter is a \"digital town square\" that should be all-encompassing, like WeChat.",
            "needle": "Elon Musk is no longer X Corp.'s CEO.",
            "context_length": 5000,
            "depth_percent": 75.0,
            "question": "How long has Elon Musk been X Corp.'s CEO?",
            "frequency": 2,
            "hallucination_type": "Excess Incorrect Retrieval"
        }
    ]
}